questions = [{'timestamps': '11/05/2022 14:40:58'}, {'question': 'Generic Angular Components - Optional Bindings', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/36024412', 'summary': 'I want to create a bunch of generic component (angular 1.5) with multiple optional binding that would be used inside multiple applications. I am afraid it will create a lot of unnecessary watchers ...', 'answers': '5', 'votes': '41', 'tags': 'javascript angularjs angularjs-directive'}, {'question': 'Textarea resizes and triggers best_in_place blur event', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/17293272', 'summary': 'I\'m using the best_in_place gem on several textareas and sometimes (seemingly randomly) the textarea \'jumps\' and triggers the blur event when I click save, prompting the "discard your changes&...', 'answers': '4', 'votes': '38', 'tags': 'javascript html ruby-on-rails ruby-on-rails-3.2'}, {'question': "Can't access prototype function in jQuery plugin", 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/34421989', 'summary': "I'm trying to create an image gallery consisting of multiple 360 degree images. I wanted to use Valiant360 for this, since it seemed to do all I needed it to do. The initiation through Angular ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '35', 'tags': 'javascript jquery angularjs'}, {'question': 'Why does Chrome run transform animation on the main thread in some cases, and not in others?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/55507749', 'summary': 'What is the criteria? In the following example, I am animating CSS transform, and when you click anywhere (while in Google Chrome) the animation is blocked by a 2-second-long while loop. Why is the ...', 'answers': 0, 'votes': '32', 'tags': 'javascript css css-transitions css-animations css-transforms'}, {'question': 'How to include zone.js, reflect-metadata etc. in Systemjs builder task?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/40528480', 'summary': "I'm using system.js and systemjs builder to create a dist folder with all the packed javascript files of my angular2 application. It works pretty nicely, except that it does not include the following ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '32', 'tags': 'javascript angular systemjs systemjs-builder'}, {'question': 'Isotope v2 filtering with Infinite Scroll - Filter not finding all items and Window not resizing on filter', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/23895457', 'summary': 'Head\'s up! There\'s a pending feature-request issue on Isotope\'s GitHub repo that you should add a "üëç" reaction to if you\'re interested in seeing official docs and demos for this (how to combine ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '32', 'tags': 'javascript jquery filter jquery-isotope infinite-scroll'}, {'question': 'Karma reload debug.html on test file changes', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/36606741', 'summary': 'When running Karma with autoWatch: true and singleRun: false, any change to my unit test files causes the tests to be re-run, and refreshes the Karma webpage at localhost:9876: The problem is that ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '29', 'tags': 'javascript webpack karma-runner'}, {'question': 'Visual Studio 2017, JavaScript intellisense inconsistencies', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/43079954', 'summary': 'TL;DR: How do you include a tsconfig.json file in Visual Studio 2017 and still have JavaScript intellisense work like it does by default, giving code hints both for your own code and 3rd-party ...', 'answers': '2', 'votes': '28', 'tags': 'javascript typescript intellisense visual-studio-2017 tsconfig'}, {'question': 'WKWebView loads HTML content too slowly in iOS9 using swift', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/35082806', 'summary': "I have been trying to integrate the WKWebView as a subview of another webview in a UIViewController. I've been able to load the content and communicate properly with the swift and javascript. However, ...", 'answers': 0, 'votes': '27', 'tags': 'javascript ios swift2 ios9 wkwebview'}, {'question': 'swf respondDecisionTaskCompleted call, response time degrade overtime', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/42464585', 'summary': 'We have a decided worker running and as the time goes we noticed the response time of the respondDecisionTaskCompleted call was getting slower and slower. We tried using the same instance of SWF ...', 'answers': 0, 'votes': '25', 'tags': 'javascript flash aws-sdk'}, {'question': 'Is there a polyfill for getIntersectionList, getEnclosureList, checkIntersection, checkEnclosure for Firefox SVG?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/34893707', 'summary': 'SVG 1.1 Support in Firefox: SVGSVGElement: Unimplemented bindings: getIntersectionList, getEnclosureList, checkIntersection, checkEnclosure, deselectAll SVG 1.1 spec: 5.11.2 Interface ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '25', 'tags': 'javascript firefox svg'}, {'question': 're-enable disabled menu "save video as" chrome ext or chrome itself "Save Video As"', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/39360975', 'summary': 'How can I re-enable the "Save Video As" option when it is disabled on a video? This is basically the opposite of this question. Is there a global command I can send to the chrome command line which ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '24', 'tags': 'javascript html google-chrome'}, {'question': 'How to convert a nested json object into an excel table using the xlsx npm library?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/56598405', 'summary': "I've got a nested json object. For the sake of simplicity: data = {'key1': 1, 'key2': 2, 'key3': {'nestedKey1': 3, 'nestedKey2': 4}} A real object is bigger but the point is that it's a nested one. ...", 'answers': '2', 'votes': '24', 'tags': 'javascript angular xlsx sheetjs'}, {'question': "Trigger 'dummy' mouse wheel event", 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/9404406', 'summary': "Is there a way to trigger a scroll wheel event with an arbitrary delta. Just like jQuery does with 'click' like: $('#selector').trigger('click'); I need something like that just with an scrollwheel ...", 'answers': '10', 'votes': '24', 'tags': 'javascript jquery mouseevent mousewheel scrollwheel'}, {'question': "How to modify the first pageNumber or execute JS in header or footer template with Chrome DevTools Protocol's printToPDF", 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/52729615', 'summary': "I'm using Headless Chrome to print out PDF files by using the printToPDF CDP method. If we set displayHeaderFooter parameter to true, then we can set specific page header and footer by using the ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '23', 'tags': 'javascript html pdf-generation google-chrome-devtools google-chrome-headless'}, {'question': 'React Native - iOS - Local image invisible (works on android)', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/52009251', 'summary': "I'm mapping TouchableOpacity with an Image nested inside of it. It works great on Android but on iOS the image is invisible. There is still a 75x75 touchable opacity that I can tap but the image is ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '23', 'tags': 'javascript ios reactjs react-native expo'}, {'question': 'Dropzone.js no longer uploading multiple imgs to website on Android', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/31442122', 'summary': 'Up until about a couple weeks ago, my web app was working great on desktop and mobile, using dropzone.js as a drag and drop means of uploading images. Now suddenly on my Android device things have ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '22', 'tags': 'javascript dropzone.js'}, {'question': 'How can I get the stack trace for a JavaScript exception in IE 8?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/15810402', 'summary': 'When a JavaScript exception is thrown in IE 8, how can I see its stack trace? For example, the following code from jQuery catches an exception and rethrows it. Debugging in Visual Studio (2012), ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '22', 'tags': 'javascript debugging exception internet-explorer-8 stack-trace'}, {'question': 'Adding a script to an Angular Library', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/50990388', 'summary': 'I am trying to export some components of my Angular 6 application into a library. Unfortunately, I need to use a WebToolkit to connect to a proprietary service build by other people, which is only ...', 'answers': '2', 'votes': '21', 'tags': 'javascript angular angular-cli'}, {'question': 'Uploading File in parts using XMLHttpRequest and auth digest', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/50840417', 'summary': 'I am trying to upload a local mp4/movie file with XMLHttpRequest() on a server. This is written with react-native and in a final version user would be able to upload any big files from his/her IOS/...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '21', 'tags': 'javascript react-native upload xmlhttprequest blob'}, {'question': 'Cross Origin in ajax not working for .properties file in IOS (10.3.1)', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/44717999', 'summary': 'I used i18n plugin for load *.properties file for translation and its working fine on android platform but same library not working on IOS 10.3.1. It gives me below error: i have done some changes in ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '21', 'tags': 'javascript jquery ios ajax ios10.3'}, {'question': 'Embedding react-boilerplate in Rails 5.1', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/43137712', 'summary': 'Has anyone tried integrating react-boilerplate into a Ruby on Rails 5.1 app? It looks like the 5.1 approach to embedding React components in views is fairly simple. Rails 5.1 is using webpacker which ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '21', 'tags': 'javascript ruby-on-rails webpack react-boilerplate'}, {'question': 'Add iOS speech recognition support for web app?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/28592170', 'summary': 'Currently, the HTML5 web speech api works great on google chrome for all devices except mobile iOS. Text-to-speech works, but speech-to-text is not supported. webkitSpeechRecognition is not supported. ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '21', 'tags': 'javascript ios html google-chrome speech-recognition'}, {'question': 'Replace Maven Archetype property in JavaScript file', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/24698956', 'summary': "I'm trying to create a Maven Archetype for a Java web app and I have some JavaScript files I want it to generate. Is it possible to use Maven Archetype properties in the JavaScript file such that it ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '21', 'tags': 'javascript maven properties maven-archetype'}, {'question': 'Copy to clipboard BINARY data in browsers', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/13848337', 'summary': 'State of the art in Copy to Clipboard feature (My investigations) Flash alternative I have found the following alternatives: Zclip: we are using zeroclipboard (ancestor, zclip uses its button flash ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '21', 'tags': 'javascript flash coffeescript clipboard'}, {'question': 'The simplest way to solve gimbal lock when using DeviceOrientation events in javascript - How to make a perfect spirit level/bubble level app', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/69216465', 'summary': 'Starting with... window.addEventListener("deviceorientation", handleDeviceTilt); function handleDeviceTilt(event){ // Here we can use event.beta, event.gamma // Note that we don\'t need event....', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '21', 'tags': 'javascript device-orientation deviceorientationevent'}, {'question': 'jQuery ajax() function is ignoring dataType parameter in Firefox', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/17431081', 'summary': 'I\'m trying to use jQuery.ajax() to fetch some html, but Firefox is giving me a "junk after document element" error message. As explained here and here the problem seems to be that Firefox is expecting ...', 'answers': '3', 'votes': '21', 'tags': 'javascript ajax jquery firefox'}, {'question': 'Vue.js: inconsistent "Unknown Custom Element" that\'s resolved on a HMR', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/60422248', 'summary': 'I am familiar with component registration. This is not the low-hanging fruit related to: Vue.js component Unknown custom element Unknown custom element when nesting components in Vue.js The Problem ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '20', 'tags': 'javascript typescript vue.js webpack vuetify.js'}, {'question': 'Having trouble working with SelectWoo instances of Select2 within WooCommerce', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/56386378', 'summary': "I am using Select2 within WooCommerce in some of my own custom areas and I am targeting it with some code to add and removes certain classes and it's working fine except for the SelectWoo instances ...", 'answers': 0, 'votes': '20', 'tags': 'javascript jquery woocommerce jquery-select2 jquery-select2-4'}, {'question': 'Drag and drop issue in Chrome related to Windows scale (125%)', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/52407557', 'summary': "I have an issue with drag and drop on Chrome (v69.0.3497.100). Specifically, some of the drag and drop events are getting fired when Windows scaling is other than 100% even though they shouldn't be ...", 'answers': '2', 'votes': '20', 'tags': 'javascript html google-chrome drag-and-drop'}, {'question': 'Recaptcha V3 error incorrect-captcha-sol randomly', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/67935841', 'summary': "I'm getting incorrect-captcha-sol error code sometime while using Google reCAPTCHA server side verification api. I have integrated google recaptcha validation to some of my apis. To do so, I pass ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '20', 'tags': 'javascript recaptcha recaptcha-v3'}, {'question': 'Looking for a Dual Listbox with AngularJS and Bootstrap', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/38101913', 'summary': 'I am looking for a component like this to be included in my project: http://geodan.github.io/duallistbox/sample-100.html I want to install it with npm. The problem is that I tested some of the ...', 'answers': '3', 'votes': '19', 'tags': 'javascript angularjs twitter-bootstrap npm'}, {'question': "Play multiple instances of an html5's Audio object", 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/4728352', 'summary': "I'm making a small game in Javascript and it requires some audio for better user experience. The main issue I have is that I have to play 1 song/sound multiple times, and sometimes at the same time. ...", 'answers': '3', 'votes': '19', 'tags': 'javascript html audio'}, {'question': 'Jasmine: How to mock MutationObserver?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/50398703', 'summary': 'I have a angularjs component, HTML template <div id="panel" class="hide-div"> <div id="viewPort" class="hide-div"> ... </div> </div> JS var myController = ...', 'answers': 0, 'votes': '18', 'tags': 'javascript angularjs jasmine karma-jasmine mutation-observers'}, {'question': 'How to minify and factor-bundle files in the same browserify command?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/32018901', 'summary': 'I currently have this factor-bundle command which I use to bundle my files, and pull everything common into a common file: browserify index.js bar-charts.js list-filter.js dashboard.js -p [ factor-...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '18', 'tags': 'javascript browserify uglifyjs factor-bundle'}, {'question': 'Generate PDF using EVOPdf, WebAPI and AngularJS', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/31934297', 'summary': "I'm having an issue rendering a PDF using EVOPdf from a WebAPI controller to an AngularJS app. This is my code so far: Angular call: var url = 'api/form/build/' + id; $http.get(url, null, { ...", 'answers': '3', 'votes': '18', 'tags': 'javascript angularjs pdf asp.net-web-api evopdf'}, {'question': 'Incorrect line numbers - sourcemaps, Webpack 2 Typescript', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/45225076', 'summary': 'This issue occurs in Chrome 59.0.3071.115 and Firefox 54.0.1 I have been doing a lot of research on trying to get correct line numbers for my Typescript source code using Webpack 2.2.1 and the open-...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '18', 'tags': 'javascript angular google-chrome typescript webpack'}, {'question': 'Unable to import webpack-bundled UMD library as an ES6 import', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/54818030', 'summary': "I've authored a javascript library using Webpack. The entrypoint someClass.js looks like this: import x from './x' /* several more imports here */ class SomeClass {} export default SomeClass; My ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '17', 'tags': 'javascript node.js webpack ecmascript-6 module'}, {'question': 'Accessing API works fine with cURL but not with Fetch API', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/53506848', 'summary': 'I know this has been addressed a lot of times on SO, but all the answers are mostly in the vein of "add a certain header to the server". In this case, the API (Shopify) works perfectly fine and can ...', 'answers': 0, 'votes': '17', 'tags': 'javascript curl shopify fetch-api'}, {'question': 'Change responseType in Axios based on response', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/53230205', 'summary': "I've an axios request with responseType: 'arraybuffer' this works correctly when response is a success 200. However when the api I'm accessing and returns a 500 with a json object - axios encodes ...", 'answers': 0, 'votes': '17', 'tags': 'javascript axios'}, {'question': 'Rails Activestorage + DirectUpload javascript progress bar not showing when using "remote:true"', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/52583138', 'summary': 'I have been using Rails ActiveStorage DirectUpload in my Rails app. And here is the code of the form: <h3>Select Files To Upload</h3> <%= form_for @uploader, url: uploaders_file_path(@...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '17', 'tags': 'javascript ruby-on-rails ruby-on-rails-5 rails-activestorage'}, {'question': 'vue-cli build a lib from component and import it', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/51772729', 'summary': 'I\'m using vue-cli for build my lib with this command: "build": "vue-cli-service build --target lib --name myLib ./src/component.vue" How can I import my component from the dist folder after the ...', 'answers': '2', 'votes': '17', 'tags': 'javascript vue.js vuejs2 vue-component vue-cli'}, {'question': 'Updating AngularJS scope after validating search form in Symfony2', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/35056544', 'summary': "Hi fellow developers, We have to rewrite a software application in Symfony2 with AngularJS, we use Symfony2 for the MVC purpose and AngularJS for the useful functions. Here's our problem, we first ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '17', 'tags': 'javascript php angularjs json symfony'}, {'question': 'Change data id onclick', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/33754789', 'summary': 'I need to change data-matchId value when user clicks a button. I can get value on click but can not set it to data-matchId. HTML Part: <script id="betradar" type="text/javascript&...', 'answers': '4', 'votes': '17', 'tags': 'javascript html jquery dom'}, {'question': 'How to add Spine animation to Phaser game?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/27154988', 'summary': 'I am new to Phaser and the whole javascript games, and I am trying to add Spine animation to Phaser. Is there a way to do that? I also tried to play my animation using Pixi.js and it worked. Also I ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '17', 'tags': 'javascript animation phaser-framework pixi.js'}, {'question': 'yielding from an iterator callback used inside a generator', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/24967314', 'summary': 'Has anyone tried to get Underscore JS or lodash (or any ES5 standard functions for that matter) working with generators? If we have an array var myArray = [1,2,3,4,6]; We want to forEach over it. In ...', 'answers': '1', 'votes': '17', 'tags': 'javascript function generator ecmascript-6 yield-keyword'}, {'question': "Get Download Url after firebase's resize extension completed", 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/58172698', 'summary': "This is what I am trying to achieve, implement the firebase's resize image extension, upload an image, then when the resize is completed, add that dowloadUrl's thumbs to a Cloud Firestore document. ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '17', 'tags': 'javascript firebase google-cloud-functions firebase-storage'}, {'question': 'Html2Canvas problems with thai language', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/31579565', 'summary': 'Run this code and then \'save\' you will difference of image. Any solution to solved this problem? Example of code $(document).on("click", "#save", function() { html2canvas( $("body"), { ...', 'answers': '2', 'votes': '17', 'tags': 'javascript jquery screenshot html2canvas'}, {'question': 'JavaScript - Draggable Gallery Slider', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/65533041', 'summary': "I'm using a function from W3Schools as a starter point to make a draggable gallery slider (.slider-all-items in my code). Few lines have been removed from the original, to prevent dragging vertically. ...", 'answers': '1', 'votes': '16', 'tags': 'javascript jquery'}, {'question': 'SQL on top of apache arrow in-browser?', 'links': 'https://stackoverflow.com/questions/56606447', 'summary': 'I have data that is stored on a client\'s browser in-memory. For example, let\'s say the dataset is as follows: "name" (string), "age" (int32), "isAdult" (bool) "Tom" , 29 ...', 'answers': '2', 'votes': '16', 'tags': 'javascript webassembly apache-arrow dremio'}]